good morning everyone this is peach
bashal so for today i'm going to share
with you all
how does set for health works set for
health is one of the best selling
products of
fwd so it's a comprehensive protection
with up to three times claim against 42
major critical illnesses
or your money back if zero claim
so i know how should i go work let's
make an example
um some assured the pago no 1 million so
how
set for health works so this is the
policy effective date
so this illustration is assuming five
years payment
so five years of payment perimeter
option 10 years or 20 years
so the longer the paying period
so this is the illustration now so for
example
on policy year one i diagnosed
a client no major critical illness in
coronary heart disease
one is one million pesos because that is
our sum
assured so that's the first claim
or why is let fwd give that money
to you so that's the first claim so
assuming on policy year two is
minor critical illness or early stage
breast cancer
so fwd will give you 20
of your sum assured which is 200 000
pesos so 20
num1 million is 200 000 pesos for a
minor claim
and assuming on policy
another major critical illness of benign
brain tumor
this is going to be your claim tree so
another one million for you
para and
on policy year five another major
critical illness bacterial meningitis so
this is going to be the claim for so
another one million pesos
so major critical illness benefit you
will receive hundred percent of your sum
assured for each
of the three major critical illness
claim plus wave all your future premiums
upon diagnosis of your first major
critical illness
year one
[Music]
so there's no major critical illness has
been paid to you
so what will happen is maroon comedy
received a healthy life benefit
which is you will receive 100 of all
all your or total premiums
fwd at the age 75.
it's just like you're saving while being
protected
what if in case the unthinkable happens
in between and
so maron getting death benefit or
insurance and we will give
your beneficiaries a lump sum payment of
of your sum assured which is one million
if in case
75 so another 1 million a month for your
family
that's 1 million 2 million 3 million
3.2 plus another 1 million that's total
of 4.2 million
pesos coverage for you
for your peace of mind you don't for
sure you don't want to be a burden to
your family when you get sick
tamar
you don't want to be a burden so i
recommend for you to get
accept for health plan
insurance whatever
so that's how set for health plan works
only here in fwd so if you're interested
to get this set for health plan we have
a digital
set for health products i'll put the
link down below
you click on linkedin if you want to get
a set for health plan
worth one million pesos but if you want
more than one million pesos
and then i suggest before you buy
this kind of
[Music]
and i can give you a recommendation as
well so let's do financial planning
it's for free no commitment at all
so what are you waiting for act now
while you are healthy while you are
capable
and while you have the time this is
peach bashal
associate financial wealth manager in
fwd
hope to see you soon thank you so much
god bless us all